// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Where Is Indra Gandhi Center For Atomic Research Located?",
    answer: "Tamil Nadu,Kalpakkam",
    options: [
      "Tamil Nadu,Kalpakkam",
      "Rajasthan,Ajmer",
      "West Bengal,Kolkata",
      "Punjab,Chandigrah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Full Form Of Amul",
    answer: "Anand Milk Union Limited",
    options: [
      "America Milk Union Limited",
      "Aman Milk United Limited",
      "Anand Milk Union Limited",
      "Anil Milk Union Limted"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who Was The First Women Judge Of The High Court?",
    answer: "Fatima Biwi",
    options: [
    "Fatima Biwi",
      "Gyan Sugha Misra",
      "Sujata Manohar",
      "Ruma Pal"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who Invented Python?",
    answer: "Guido Van Rossum",
    options: [
      "HÃ¥kon Wium Lie",
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "Guido Van Rossum",
      "Lord Lytton"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Where Is The Headquarters Of UNESCO Located?",
    answer: "Paris",
    options: [
      "Paris",
      "Tokyo",
      "California",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who invented HTML?",
    answer: "Tim Berners Lee",
    options: [
      "Tim Berners Lee",
      "Lord Canning",
      "Wium Lie",
      "Guido Van Rossum"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which Party Was Formd Of India By A.U Hume?",
    answer: "India National Congress",
    options: [
      "India National Congress",
      "Bhartiya Janta Party",
      "Communist Party OF India",
      "Communist Party Of India (Marxist)"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Near Which River Statue Of Unity Located?",
    answer: "Narmada River",
    options: [
      "Sabarmati River",
      "Godavri River",
      "Kaveri River",
      "Narmada River"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Where Is Silicon Valley Located?",
    answer: "California,U.S",
    options: [
      "Heroshima,Japan",
      "Bengaluru,Karnataka",
      "California,U.S",
      "Bejing,China"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In Which Year Was The Reserve Bank Of India Established?",
    answer: "1935",
    options: [
      "1949",
      "1939",
      "1940",
      "1935"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "When was Shri Lata Mangeshkar Died?",
    answer: "6 Feb 2022",
    options: [
      "2 Feb 2022",
      "6 Feb 2022",
      "10 Feb 2022",
      "9 Feb 2022"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "1024 Kilobytes is equal to?",
    answer: "1 Megabyte (MB)",
    options: [
      "0.5 Megabyte (kb)",
      "1 Megabyte (MB)",
      "5 Megabyte (MB)",
      "1.5 Megabyte (MB)"
    ]
  },

];